# **Benjamin Papac**

## Software Engineer (Full-Stack)

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/benpapac | GitHub: https://github.com/benpapac

#### **SKILLS**

**Software Engineering:** React, Javascript, Typescript, Python, GeoJSON, Google Maps API, Redux; AWS; Docker; GitHub; GraphQL; front end engineering, back end engineering;

Soft Skills: Leadership, attention to detail, communication, openness to criticism, problem solving, technological adaptability

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a Full-Stack Software Engineer with 2 years experience in my new field after transitioning from the entertainment industry. I have measurable experience in a large scale Precision Ag organization, John Deere ISG, which has a significant amount of overlap with PACES' technical needs to help customers build clean energy projects. These include, but are not limited to: AWS deployment, map frameworks, data-heavy infrastructure, and complex data management, especially data about <u>land</u>.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Software Engineer (Full-Stack), John Deere ISG

Mar 2023 - Nov 2024

- Plan product roadmap with product managers, UX designers, and devops
- Create preview of a new product (AutoPath) using the in-app map, yielding 60% user engagement (measured using Adobe Analytics)
- Update UX feature (AutoPath) to improve user experience, reducing click count by 8 to 10 clicks
- Update api contract for AutoPath feature, improving separation between two types of data, Boundaries and AutoPath
- Conduct data analytics through Databricks
- Leveraged IntelliJ's CoPilot AI to improve work speed by 10%
- Develop end to end products within large, complex infrastructure
- Participate in customer research meetings, talk to users and learn their needs
- Programming Languages and Frameworks: Javascript, Typescript, Python, React, Redux, Java, Google Maps

#### Software Engineer (Full-Stack) Intern, Amotions INC.

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

- Build React Components in a Next.js app
- Participate in weekly standups
- Update training and onboarding documentation, assist in standardizing codebase for maintainability
- Train other interns in React and Next.js
- Refactor, debug and optimize existing code, reducing code weight by 10%

#### Harry Potter & the Cursed Child

Aug 2019 - Sep 2022

#### Actor

- Handle high-pressure, technically demanding scenarios with a live audience
- Adapt to new and unexpected challenges in a constantly changing environment
- Have a bias toward action and prioritize execution, particularly when the unexpected happens on stage
- Develop "soft," skills, including empathy, interpersonal communication, and public speaking

### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly, Full Stack Web Development, Certification

Nov 2021

Louisiana State University, B.A. Mass Communication, Magna Cum Laude

May 2014